

126 Nguyen Cu Trinh, Nguyen Cu Trinh Ward, District 1, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

□ (+84) 16-3511-4115 | 🚾 daoquocvuong@gmail.com | 🖸 blackwine93v | 🛅 blackwine93v

"You cannot solve a problem with the same mind that created it" -ALBERT EINSTEIN

## Summary\_

As a Software Engineer, I have more than 3.5 years of experience in designing, building software on the web and mobile platforms. With the enthusiasm of youth, I am confident I can contribute my abilities to the development of the company, glad to share my knowledge with everyone, I think "Learning to share, sharing to learn". Innovative, flexible in making good solutions to solve complex problems, ready to learn new technologies if needed. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to learn JavaScript's frameworks (specializes in ReactJS).

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Taembe - Pagoda Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

**FULLSTACK ENGINEER** 

Jan. 2016 - March 2017

- · Built and maintenance an e-commerce website in Vietnam that provide products for mom and baby, such as diapers, milk, and related items.
- Designed and implemented UI/UX in web application (ReactJS, Bootstrap).
- Implemented Restful API in Node.js Hapi.
- Integrated SendGrid, Mixpanel, Social authentication and online payment Stripe.
- Migrated and cloned Tamebe USA from Taembe Vietnam.
- · Designed and built Taembe Android app.

### **Sunrise Software Solution**

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

FULLSTACK ENGINEER

April. 2017 - August. 2018

- · Collaborated with delivery director, project managers, and designers to develop web applications (ReactJS, AngularJS), mobile applications (React Native, Ionic).
- Organized training sessions for company employees on ReactJS (2 sessions).
- Supported other teams to build a development environment on web and mobile applications.
- As a member in S3 Mobile Key team, supported to provide solutions for mobile projects.
- Won the 4th prize in the Robotic Creation Competition at the company.

### PROJECT TRIPPER. MATKA- JA KULULASKUT

- · Built Android and iOS applications using React Native, support automatically make a travel invoice with a calendar entry and add all receipts to customer book without writing a word.
- Implemented and enhanced new features in the application (Social authentication,..)

### PROJECT THX STANDARD

- Built a Single Page Application website Angular JS serverless. This web application helps user to pick product and compare them about price, feature, specific information.
- Built development and production enviroment.
- Analyzed, customized so that the application can achieve the best performance.

#### PROJECT EYEVIEW - INSIGHTUS

- · Built a web application allows tracking public cameras of Australia government. This also allows managing, monitoring, viewing and making live stream on these cameras, it is integrated 2D/3D geographical map.
- · Config development environment on Webpack, Docker.
- Designed and implemented UI/UX in AngularJS, Bootstrap.
- Integrated interactive Leaflet (2D map), Cesium (3D map), HLS live streaming video.

### **Presentation**

### **ReactJS 101 Workshop**

SPEAKER AT NEIGHBORHUB CO-WORKING SPACE

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

Nov. 2017

• Introduced the ReactJS which is for the modern web application development.

• Introduced how to ReactJS works and demo a real ReactJS application.

Vuong Dao · Résumé AUGUST 13, 2018

December, 2017

PRESENTER FOR < SUNRISE SOFTWARE SOLUTION'S EMPLOYEES>

- Supported frontend developers in company get to understand ReactJS, its concepts, how to use React in real projects.
- Introduced the ReactJS which is for the modern web application development.
- Shared common use cases, best practices when using ReactJS.

# **Techinical Expertise**

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLSET

- · Strong in JavaScript and its modern frameworks.
- Web frameworks: ReactJS/Redux, AngularJS, NodeJS, NextJS, CSS Preprocessors (SASS/LESS), Responsive, Single Page Application, Progressive Web Apps.
- Mobile frameworks: React Native, Ionic, Flutter, Android Native.
- Database: Relational DB(MySQL), Non-relational DB (CouchDB, PouchDB, MongoDB), Firebase.
- Design patterns: Singleton, Modular, Prototype, Observer, MVP, MVC.
- Object-Oriented, Event-Oriented, Functional Programming, Restful API, GraphQL, Falcor.

### **WORKING KNOWLEDGE**

- · Java, PHP, Dart, Python.
- Desktop appication: ElectronJS.
- Experienced in building Chatbot (use Api.ai), Arduino robotics (IoT, automation), Video calling (WebRTC, SocketIO)
- Style coding, Unit testing.

### **TOOLS**

- Git.
- OS platforms: Windows, Linux, OSX.
- Vim, tmux, crontab.
- Development tools: Webpack, Gulp, Vagrant, Docker, AWS, NGINX.

### **Education**

#### **University Of Science, HCMC**

**B.S. IN COMPUTER NETWORKING** 

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet nam

2011 - 2015

Got a Scholarship.

• GPA: 8.41